Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 2010, 5
    - 3/11--Intel, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - 3/13--Vanguard, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 3/15--Procter Gamble green campaign, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - 3/17--Body Shop, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - 3/17--Garrett Weber-Gale, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - 3/17--Kantar, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - 3/19--ESPN/Jim Beam, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - 3/22--Marketing during crisis, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - 3/24--JWT, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - 3/24--Travelocity, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - 3/25--Allstate, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - 3/26--Mootopia, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - 3/29--Hyundai/Christopher Perry, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - 3/29--Ogilvy/Salesmanship, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - 3/29--TCM network, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - 3/30--Kirshenbaum Bond Senecal, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - 3/30--Product Red, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - 3/31--Lexus/Skinny, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - 3/31--Nivea/AVP Tour, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - 3/31--Powerade, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - 3/31--Six flags, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - 4/1--Dr. Martens, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - 4/1--Pirate brands, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - 4/5--Carol Cone, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - 4/5--Chipotle, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - 4/5--Creative conflict (CareerBuilder vs Levi's Super Bowl ads), 2010 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - 4/5--Dairy Queen, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - 4/5--Diapers.com, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - 4/5--Reebok, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - 4/6--Oxygen Upfront, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - 4/7--FX Upfront, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - 4/8--Animal Planet, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - 4/8--AT, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - 4/8--Nike/Tiger Woods, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - 4/9--Bahamas, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - 4/9--Bertolli/Logo, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - 4/9--BrandLab, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - 4/11--Zeta Interactive/Tiger Woods, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - 4/12--Stanley Steemer, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - 4/13--CNN Upfront, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - 4/13--Good Housekeeping magazine, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - 4/13--Monk-E-Mail/CareerBuilder, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - 4/14--BET Upfront, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - 4/14--Crowdsourcing, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 4/14--Shaun White/Target, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - 4/14--Telemundo, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - 4/15--American Idiot/Motorola, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - 4/15--BGTwo, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - 4/15--Stella Artois, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - 4/16--ICOM/Kurdistan, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - 4/16--Belvedere vodka, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - 4/16--Lori Senecal, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - 4/16--Sex the City II, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - 4/19--D'Agostino, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - 4/20--Baseball, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - 4/20--Hoover, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - 4/20--McCann poaching lawsuit, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - 4/20--MoFilm, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - 4/20--Palazzo Advisory/Acquisition, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - 4/20--Scripps, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - 4/20--Sex the City II, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - 4/21--PETA/Bea Arthur, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - 4/22--Cash for Consumers, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - 4/22--Hunter PR/Bring Your Parents to Work Day, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - 4/23--Chevrolet, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - 4/26--Benjamin Moore, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - 4/26--Kodak, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - 4/27--FTC ad literacy campaign, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - 4/27--Method detergent vs. Clorox, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - 4/27--NBC Upfront, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - 4/27--Religious campaigns, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - 4/28--BrandZ, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - 4/28--Six Flags, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - 4/28--Wishbone, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - 4/29--Norelco/Philips, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - 4/29--Product Red, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - 4/30--Bing, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - 4/30--Gatorade G Series Pro, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - 4/30--New Jersey, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - 4/30--Office Max, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - 5/3--Blip.TV/7-Eleven, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - 5/3--Joey Pants, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - 5/4--Proactiv, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - 5/5--Cyrus Mehri/NAACP, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - 5/5--Pizza, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - 5/6--Procter Gamble, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - 5/6--Tony Awards, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - 5/7--Modern Family/Twilight Zone, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - 5/7--Sundance Channel/Day Night Day Night, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - 5/7--TV Upfronts, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - 5/10--JetBlue, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - 5/10--Rhode Island Community Food Bank "Nothing" campaign, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - 5/12--Rodgers Hammerstein, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - 5/13--2(X)ist, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - 5/13--Telemundo Upfront, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - 5/14--Clearwater Corporation, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - 5/14--Corona Light, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - 5/14--Frankness in ads, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - 5/14--Purpose Agency, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - 5/17--Common Cents, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - 5/17--Jewish Federation, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - 5/18--TV Upfronts, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - 5/19--TV Upfronts, 2010; 2 folders (Box 92, Folder 16-17)
    - 5/21--Chevrolet, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - 5/21--TV Upfronts, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - 5/24--TV Upfronts, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - 5/24--Stolichnaya, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - 5/24--Yogi Berra/IXP ad campaign, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - 5/25--AT, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - 5/25--Oxygen Media/Yoplait/Dance Your Ass Off Tour, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - 5/26--Kantar ad spending, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - 5/26--Lay's, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - 5/26--Popeye's, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - 5/27--Kia Soul, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - 5/27--Kraft, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - 5/27--USA/Growing Pains (series), 2010 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - 5/27--Vlasic, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - 5/28--E*Trade, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - 5/28--Men's Wearhouse, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - 5/30--GoDaddy, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - 6/1--20 Questions, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - 6/1--CheapTickets, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - 6/1--Lexus, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - 6/1--Michigan State "Spartans Will" campaign, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - 6/2--Sprint, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - 6/2--TV Upfront market, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - 6/3--Google/Hearst, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - 6/4--BP (British Petroleum), 2010 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - 6/4--HSBC Tennis, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - 6/4--The Glades Book Version, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - 6/4--Upfront update, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - 6/7--Cinema ads, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - 6/7--Esurance, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - 6/7--Sabra hummus, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - 6/7--Tree Top apple juice, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - 6/7--Unilever, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - 6/7--Wrath of Cannes, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - 6/8--AICP Show, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - 6/8--CBS Upfront, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - 6/9--ABC Upfront, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - 6/9--Bols Genever, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - 6/9--Ogilvy "Brick" contest, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - 6/10--3D advertising event, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - 6/10--ABC Upfront, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - 6/10--Armani A/X, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - 6/10--Dunkin' Donuts, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - 6/11--Progressive Insurance contest, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - 6/14--Beekman Boys, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - 6/14--Chevrolet, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - 6/14--Parade Food Magazine, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - 6/14--Two Fifteen Agency, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - 6/15--PwC Entertainment/Ad spending, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - 6/16--Agency Spy, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - 6/16--Automated Media Services, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - 6/17--Starbucks, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - 6/18--Burger King, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - 6/18--Local coupons, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - 6/18--Web video, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - 6/21--Allstate, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - 6/21--Hendrich's Gin, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - 6/21--New Yorker, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - 6/21--Ogilvy "Brick" contest winner, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - 6/21--Roll Up-Blue Glass Interactive, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - 6/22--Burma: JWT and Human Rights Watch, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - 6/22--Steve Simpson, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - 6/22--World Cup, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - 6/23--Burger King, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - 6/24--Levi Strauss, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - 6/25--Gay Pride Day, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - 6/25--MDC Partners, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - 6/25--Target, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - 6/28--Bounty, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - 6/28--DLKW Lowe, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - 6/29--PQ Media, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - 6/30--Draft FCB, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - 6/30--IBM, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - 6/30--Kraft, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - 6/30--Papa John's, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - 7/1--Alex Bogusky, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - 7/1--American Legacy Foundation anti-tobacco ads, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - 7/1-9--Pinnacle, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - 7/2--Brita, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - 7/2--Butler University/Product Red, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - 7/2--Cadillac, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - 7/6--FanGo, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - 7/7--Mad Men/Banana Republic, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - 7/7--Yingli Solar, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - 7/7-9--Lebron James "The Decision" sponsors, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - 7/8--GE Capital, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - 7/8--MDC/Zig/Crispin Porter Bogusky, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - 7/8--Out-of-home/Clear Channel, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - 7/8--Saks/Barney's, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - 7/9--Bank of America/Major League Baseball, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - 7/9--ESPN ads, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - 7/9--Milk/Dentists, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - 7/10--Kraft iPad recipes, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - 7/11--San Pellegrino, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - 7/12--Kind snacks, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - 7/12--Media Kitchen/Test Kitchen, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - 8/2--Meredith/Jack Griffin, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - 8/3--CheapTickets, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - 8/3--Unilever/Mad Men, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - 8/4--American Legacy "Truth" campaign, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - 8/6--Joel Ewanick (GM), 2010 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - 8/6--Teen Choice Awards, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - 8/9--MTV Tee-Jay, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - 8/9--Van Gogh vodka, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - 8/10--Experian/Victorious Secrets (musical group), 2010 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - 8/12--JetBlue, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - 8/12--Glee (series)/Macy's, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - 8/13--Car ads, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - 8/13--Lee Jeans, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - 8/16--LGBT/Real estate, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - 8/16--Boardwalk Empire (series), 2010 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - 8/17--Burger King, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - 8/17--New Era hats, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - 8/18--Haribo (Gummy Bears), 2010 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - 8/19--Acumen/Ferragamo, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - 8/19--AlphaBird, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - 8/19--New Yorker Festival, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - 8/19--Pizza Hut, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - 8/20--Hawai'I 5-0 (series), 2010 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - 8/20--Kraft Huddle to Fight Hunger, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - 8/20--Mad Men/Time Life Building, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - 8/23--Honda, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - 8/23--Sweet 'n Low, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - 8/25--LG/Jane Lynch, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - 8/25--Nissan, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - 8/25--Popeye's, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - 8/27--8th Continent, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - 8/27--Domino's, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - 8/27--Euro RSCG, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - 8/27--Stand Up to Cancer, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - 8/30--Truth Zombies, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - 9/7--Portugal Cork, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - 9/8--Glamour, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - 9/9--Kwittken Co., 2010 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - 9/13--CCFC (Campaign for a Commercial-Free Childhood)/Zevo-3, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - 9/13--Xerox, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 9/15--Domino's, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 9/15--Newspaper National Network, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - 9/15--Skechers, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - 9/16--Television Bureau, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - 9/17--Ally Financial, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - 9/17--BP/ARCO, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - 9/17--Co: (agency), 2010 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - 9/17--Walgreen's/Dr. Oz, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - 9/20--American Cancer Society, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - 9/20--Cream of Wheat/Cinnabon, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - 9/20--General Electric "Ecomagination" campaign, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - 9/20--Jennie-O, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - 9/20--New York TV Festival, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - 9/20--People's Choice Awards, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - 9/20--Tropicana Trop50, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - 9/21--Philips contest, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - 9/24--Advertising Week, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - 9/24--Electric cars, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - 9/24--Unilever/Mad Men, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - 9/27--Advertising Week, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - 9/27--Bloomberg/JWT, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - 9/28--Advertising Week, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 9/28--Nancy Pelosi/Jeff Zucker, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - 9/29--Advertising Week, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - 9/29--TD Ameritrade, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - 9/30--Midnight Moment/Times Square, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 9/30--Lincoln, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - 10/1--Magazine Publishers of America, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - 10/3--Major League Baseball, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - 10/4--Advertising Week NYC, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - 10/4--Fremantle Media, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - 10/6--Halloween, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - 10/7--Craigslist TV, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - 10/7--Mitsubishi, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - 10/7--Sharecare, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - 10/8--10/10/10 as event, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - 10/8--Made Possible magazine, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - 10/12--Gap logo, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - 10/12--Retail percentage discounting, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - 10/14--JetBlue, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - 10/15--ANA (Association of National Advertisers), 2010 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - 10/18--BBE (Broadband Enterprises), 2010 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - 10/18--Chevron, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - 10/19--ANA (Association of National Advertisers), 2010 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - 10/19--Cars.com, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - 10/19--Mad Men/John Slattery advocate for same-sex marriage, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - 10/20--Ocean Spray/Disney, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - 10/21--Jon Nesvig, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - 10/22--Pink Drink with a Cause, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - 10/23--Mike Hughes/Martin Agency/Virginia Commonwealth University, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - 10/25--Healthy Weight Commitment Foundation, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 10/25--Mad Men (series), 2010 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - 10/27--Boost Mobile/N.Y. Knicks, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - 10/27--Chevrolet/World Series, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 10/28--DDB Remedy, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - 10/29--Super Bowl, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 10/29--Weather Proof Garment Co., 2010 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - 11/1--Christmas retail, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - 11/1--PR Week Cause Survey, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - 11/2--Cause marketing, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - 11/4--Edelman/Cause marketing, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - 11/5--Conan O'Brien, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - 11/5--Macy's "Yes, Virginia"/Believe, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - 11/5--Truck marketing, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - 11/8--Mr. Peanut, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - 11/8--Toyota, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - 11/9--Conan O'Brien, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - 11/9--Holidays/Bloomingdale's/J.C. Penney, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - 11/10--Holidays/Bloomingdale's/J.C. Penney, 2010 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - 11/10--Kahlua, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - 11/11--Iran and Afghanistan Veterans of America, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - 11/11--Nike "Girl Effect", 2010 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - 11/12--Ford, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - 11/15--eBay, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - 11/15--IdeaLists, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - 11/16--Macy's Black Friday, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - 11/17--Brian Tierney/Publicis, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - 11/17--Chevrolet Volt, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - 11/17--HomeAway, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - 11/18--Top Gear, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - 11/22--BBDO Batten Co., 2010 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - 11/23--Southwest Airlines/Windows, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - 11/23--USA Network, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - 11/24--S.C. Johnson, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - 11/26--Holiday Food, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - 11/26--Holiday Food, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - 11/29--20 Questions, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - 11/30--Hairdressers Against AIDS, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - 11/30--One Club, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - 12/1--Progressive Insurance, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - 12/3--Forecast, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - 12/7--Mariah Media, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - 12/7--UBS Global Media Conference, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - 12/8--All Out Global (LGBT), 2010 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - 12/10--Grey NY, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - 12/11--Best ads of the year, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - 12/11--General Mills/Care, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - 12/13--Brandon Berger/Ogilvy, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - 12/15--MDC Partners/72 and Sunny, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - 12/16--Jon Nesvig, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - 12/20--WPP JWT/Ogilvy Action, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl, 2010; 4 folders (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
    - Super Bowl--Anheuser-Busch, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Boost Mobile, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Bridgestone, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--CareerBuilder, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Chrysler/Dodge, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--Clips, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Denny's, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Diamond Foods, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Doritos, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Dove for Men, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Dr. Pepper, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Electronic Arts/Dante's Inferno, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--Focus on the Family, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--HomeAway, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--Honda, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai/Kia, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Super Bowl--Intel, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Super Bowl--KGB, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Super Bowl--Kia, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Super Bowl--Levi Dockers, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Super Bowl--Mars Snickers, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Super Bowl--Monster, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Super Bowl--Motorola, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - Super Bowl--Pre- and post-game, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Super Bowl--Question and Answer, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Super Bowl--Taco Bell, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Super Bowl--Teleflora, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Super Bowl--Tru TV, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Super Bowl--Universal Orlando, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Super Bowl--U.S. Census, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--Vizio, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--VW, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--VW/Audi, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Wrap-up, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - 2011, 6
    - 1/3--2011 outlook (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - 1/4--Kantar Media, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - 1/4--MWW Group, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - 1/4--PETA/Lea Michele, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - 1/4--(Product) Red/Penfolds/AIDS, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - 1/5--Procter Gamble "Moms"/Olympics, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - 1/6--Purex, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - 1/7--Mini Cooper, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - 1/10--Carino's Italian, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - 1/10--Clarins, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - 1/11--Cox/Adify, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - 1/11--Tostitos, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - 1/12--Aston Martin, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - 1/12--ABC/Diet Dr. Pepper, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - 1/12--Beanstalk, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - 1/12--Jon Bond/Big Fuel, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - 1/12--Stephen Colbert "Sellout", 2011 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - 1/13--Details/Bon Apetit magazines, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - 1/13--Super Bowl Audi, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - 1/14--Super Bowl CareerBuilder, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - 1/18--California Tobacco Control Program, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - 1/18--DDB Trend Hunter, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - 1/18--Hewlett Packard ePrint, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - 1/18--Honest Tea/Coca-Cola, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - 1/18--Logo Channel, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - 1/21--Super Bowl E*Trade, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - 1/22--Phyllis Robinson, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - 1/24--Bon Apetit magazine, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - 1/24--Sappi Fine Paper, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - 1/24--Super Bowl Papa John's, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - 1/25--Super Bowl Kia/Mercedes, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - 1/26--Super Bowl/VW, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - 1/28--Barbara Lippert/Goodby, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - 1/28--NBC/Turbo Tax, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - 1/28--Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - 1/31--Mount Gay Rum, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - 1/31--MTV/Skins (series), 2011; 2 folders (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
    - 2/1--Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - 2/4--Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - 2/4--Super Bowl/Papa John's, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - 2/5--Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - 2/7--Super Bowl, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - 2/7--Super Bowl preview, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - 2/8--Super Bowl/Groupon, 2011 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - 2/9--News roundup, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - 2/9--Super Bowl/Groupon, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - 2/9--Super Bowl recap, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - 2/9--Yahoo!/Diet Dr. Pepper, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - 2/10--ANA TV and Everything, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - 2/10--Super Bowl blog, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - 2/10--Super Bowl HomeAway, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - 2/10--Super Bowl postgame, 2011; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 8-9)
    - 2/11--Academy Awards, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 10)